What's going on?
なってんの?
Is there one nearby?
近くにあるかな?
Yeah, that's sad.
うん、悲しいよね
Yeah.
うん
what happened?
どうしたの?
Were you interested?
気になってた?
Yeah.
うん
Just keep this in your hands.
これの手のままでね
Yeah.
うん
Leave this.
これ残してよ
copper?
どう?
Yeah.
うん
Yeah?
うん?
Well, how does that make you feel?
えー、どういう気持ちになるの?
It's tough here.
ここはきつい
Oh, that's so tight.
おー、すごくきついね
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
It's so twirling.
すっごい、くるくるしてる
You hit red.
赤当たってるね
Yeah.
うん
Hmm, you don't have a lot of back pain.
んーごい腰痛くないだろ
Ah, that's erotic.
あー、エロい
It's so erotic.
すっごいエロいね
Can you see it completely?
まる見える?
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごい
Eh, great.
えー、ごい
Can I take it out?
出していい?
It's so erotic.
すっごいエロいね
It's coming.
てきねー
Shobikina.
しょーびてきな
What are you doing?
何してんの?
We get along well.
仲良くて
Are we good friends?
仲良くてな?
Yeah.
うん
why?
なんで?
Because it's over.
終わったから
Because it’s over?
終わったから?
A lot.
いっぱいね
Because it's over.
終わったからもね
Still not enough?
ちょっとまだ足りなくない?
how was it?
どうだった?
difficult?
難しい?
difficult.
難 しい
Hey, put your foot up here.
ちょっとさ、足をさ、片足をここに上げて
She's licking in a great position.
すっごい体勢で舐めてる
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいね
Oh, that's amazing.
おー、すごいね
Oh, it's so delicious.
おー、すっごいうまい
oh
お
-I want you to wait.
ー、 待ってほしい
I want it so bad.
すっごいほしい
Can I take it out?
出していい?